dad's wife is mom is it true is it mom is it
жена папы - это мама правда это мама
true well yes then if he is the Pope then
правда ну да то если он папа римский то
his wife who is his wife who is mom well am
его жена кто его жена кто мама римская
I right absolutely right
ну я правильно абсолютно правильно
absolutely right
абсолютно правильно
mom Nadezhda Krubskaya
мама римская Надежда Крубская
hello hello hello I am
здравствуйте здравствуйте здравствуйте я
from the city of Khmelnitsky where are you from where are you from what
из города Хмельницкий вы откуда вы
again I am from Kyiv and where are you from and where are you from
что ещё раз я из Киева а вы откуда а вы
I am not far from you
я недалеко от вас
Sudzha
суджа
Belgorod
Белгород
and you are joking are you joking
а вы шутите шутите
so that you are from Belgorod Belgorod
такжите что вы из Белгорода белгорода
show everyone Belgorod products
покажите белгородские продукты
well how can I show them to you
ну как я вам их покажу
well bring bread or milk from the refrigerator
ну хлеб или молоко из холодильника
so that it will be written there
принеси чтобы было написано там
Belgorod-manufacturer Belgorod manufacturer
Белгород-производитель белгород
and how can I show you why not
производитель а как я вам почему нет в
Belgorod is where products come from well
Белгород же поступают продукты именно ну
then and nearby from the neighboring region here
тогда и рядом из соседней области вот
show me bring milk there will be
тот покажите принесите молоко там будет
Vladivostok in any case you are somewhere here in
Владивосток по-любому вы где-то тут
any case you are somewhere here it is written
по-любому вы где-то тут написано
Belgorod region well show me well
Белгородская область ну покажите ну
show me well
покажите
this is nonsense why well come on nice
ну это бред почему ну давайте приятная
girl I also really want to know
девушка я хочу ещё действительно знать
or are you not lying many Russian women are
или вы не обманываете многие россиянки
just showing off that  they seem to be from
просто понтуются что они вроде как из
Belgorod from Belgorod I
Белгорода из Белгорода
see everything Belgorod yes I see everything Belgorod
всё вижу Белгород да всё вижу Белгород
yes it's
да
really nice and then usually uh
действительно приятно а то обычно ээ
Russian women from Moscow say: "We are from
россиянки из Москвы говорят: "Мы из
Belgorod" you just know they are having fun you
Белгорода" просто знаете им весело
know they are having fun well
знаете им весело
cool
ну круто
how are things there in Belgorod the situation is
как у вас там в Белгороде ситуация
calm the situation is calm
спокойна ситуация спокойна
well let's take the fact that it is the
ну давайте возьмём тот факт что она
same as yours it is calm
такая же как и у вас у меня спокойно у
in my city missiles do not fly in the city do not fly in
меня ракеты не летают в городе не летают
my city as in the neighboring region there are no troops of a
у меня как в соседней области нету войск
foreign state states well that means
чужого государства государства ну значит
you were just lucky and you A question yes I am a
вам просто повезло а вы А вопрос да я
streamer question how did it happen that you
стример вопрос как так получилось что вы
lived peacefully in Belgorod Kursk people
себе спокойно жили в Белгороде Куряне
lived in Kursk and then oops and then oops what
жили в Курске а тут опа а тут опа что
again
ещё раз
how old are you how old are you 20
сколько тебе лет сколько тебе лет 20
I am saying how does it happen that you
я же говорю как так получается что вы
all lived peacefully and then gop and a
все спокойно жили а потом гоп и в вашей
war came to your region well
области пришла война
I have every right not to
ну я же могу полное право иметь не
answer this question because I don't
отвечать на этот вопрос потому что я не
know a specific answer to it and what did we
знаю конкретного ответа на него а что мы
come out here to talk yes let's talk well I
вышли сюда поговорить да поговорим ну я
How did I know that you would meet
Откуда я знала что вы встретитесь
streamer
стример
okay let's I am not a streamer what are we talking about  let's
о'кей давайте я не стример о чём мы
talk about what shall we talk about no you're a
поговорим о чём мы поговорим нет вы
streamer you've already said that
стример вы уже это сказали
t if I said that I was the Pope
т если бы я скажу что я папа римский
we all know that the Pope has long been
мы все знаем чтобы римского давно уже
dead
нету в живых
[music]
[музыка]
and when did the Pope die and when did the
а когда умер папа римский а когда умер
Pope die what when did the Pope die the
папа римский что когда умер папа римский
Pope
папа римский
I don't remember
я не помню
in what century did the Pope die the
в каком столетии умер папа римский умер
Pope died yes why
папа римский да почему
okay give me a hint the Pope three
ладно давай подсказку папа римский три
options died in the 15th century in the 15th or in the 19th and
варианта умер в XV веке в XV или в XIX и
in the 19th
в девятнадцатом
let me guess and that's right
давайте я на угад скажу а там правильно
no let's guess in the 8th century let's guess
нет давайте вос век давайте угадали
really you knew you're just trolling me you're
реально вы знали вы меня троллите просто
just trolling you You knew you
вы меня троллите просто
knew well that's
вы Вы знали вы знали ну-ка
cool did you study the history of the Vatican
прикольно а вы изучали историю Ватикана
yes yes well
да да
every person in school studied history the
ну каждый человек в школе изучал историю
same way and what did they tell you like you
же и что вам говорили типа вот вы
studied the history of the Pope popes yes and the
проходили историю папы пап римских да и
Pope he lived like he died in the
папа римский он жил типа вот он умер в
16th century yes and in what century was the Pope born the
XVI веке да а в каком веке родился папа
Pope was born I do
римский родился папа римский
n't know well let's think if he was
не знаю ну давайте подумайте если он
born in the 16th  century let's give options
родился в XVI веке давайте варианты
then oh if he died in the 16th
значит ой если он умер попаримски в XVI
century then he was born in the 13th in the
веке то родился он в тринадцатом в
12th or 14th
двенадцатом или в четырнадцатом
in the 13th or 12th
в тринадцатом или двенадцатый
think think well let's guess
подумайте подумайте ну давайте
the 13th or you you know you're
тринадцатый угадала или ты ты знаешь ты
kidding or you know you're kidding no well you're [ __ ] kidding
прикалываешься или ты знаешь ты
you knew that the Pope died a
ну ты уй ты знала что папа римский умер
long time ago you guessed it's unrealistic you guessed well
давно ты угадала это нереально угадала
okay 1/3 that you guessed yes the 15th century that
ну ладно 1/3 что угадала да xv век что
he died and guessed that he was born in the 1st century and
он умер и угадал что в 1 веке он родился
you're stuck I don't care about you at all Everything-everything can be
а вы зависли я вас вообще не Всё-всё
heard from me now everything everything can be heard from me now
теперь слышно меня всё всё теперь слышно
yes
меня да
and at what age did the Pope die at what
а в каком возрасте умер папа римский
age did the Pope die
возрасте умер папа римский
I don't know well let's count look
я не знаю ну давайте посчитайте смотрите
if he was born in the 10th century and died in the 10th
если он родился в X веке а умер в X
how much will it be 18 - 13 18 - 1
сколько будет 18 - 13 18 - 1
What if the Pope was born in the 10th century and
Что если папа римский родился в X веке а
died in the 10th then take 18 - 13
умер в X вона то возьмите 18 - 13
how much will it be 13 how much will it be
сколько будет 13 сколько будет
20 years is
20 лет
correct 18 20 years and poparimsky died
правильно 18 20 лет и попаримский умер
moldom 20 years died moldom 20 years
молдым 20 лет умер молдым 20 лет
cool
круто
how much was in history because
у тебя сколько было по истории потому
you see very good history you
что ты смотрю очень хорошую историю
know very good history you know
знаешь очень хорошую историю знаешь
I don't remember
я не помню
and mathematics how much was how much was I do
а математика сколько было сколько было я
n't remember
не помню
so and the question do you remember what was the name of the Pope's wife
так а вопрос ты помнишь как звали жену
options: Anna
варианты: Анна
Yaroslavovna Nadezhda
Ярославовна Надежда
Krupskaya
Крупская
or Elizabeth the Great the
или Елизавета Великая
great no definitely not Elizabeth
великая нет точно не Елизавета потому
because Elizabeth the Great then ascended the
что Елизавета великая потом зашла на
throne
престол
and
а
so it remains Anna Yaroslavna and Nadezhda
так остаётся Анна Ярославна и Надежда
Krupskaya who is who Nadezhda Krupskaya she is
Крупская кто кто надежда Крупская она
correct yes you you knew everything you
правильно да ты ты всё знала ты всё
knew everything no and what was she famous for here is Nadezhda
знала нет а чем прославилась вот Надежда
Krupskaya who was the Pope's
Крупская которая была папы римского
wife
женой
I don't remember
я не помню
but what was her name title what was her
а как её называли титул у неё какой был
title
титул
well if her husband was the Pope then she then
ну если её муж был папа римский то она
she well damn well the
то она
Pope is the
ну блин ну папа римский - это папа
Pope and what is she well the Pope's wife who is
римский а она что ну жена папы римского
I don't know look the Pope's wife is mom
я не знаю смотри жена папы - это мама
really  this is mom really well yes then if he is the
правда это мама правда ну да то если он
Pope then his wife who is his wife
папа римский то его жена кто его жена
who is mommy well I am right
кто мама римская ну я правильно
absolutely right absolutely right
абсолютно правильно абсолютно правильно
mommy Nadezhda Krubskaya Krubskaya
мама римская надежда Крубская крубская
I understand and in what country was mommy
я поняла а в какой стране родилась мама
Nadezhda Krupskaya born
римская Надежда Крупская
I don't know really well
я не знаю правда
come on the name Nadezhda - from what
ну давай имя Надежда - это из какой
country
страны
so now in all countries you can name
так сейчас во всех странах можно назвать
a child Nadezhda so it used to be this is the
ребёнка Надеждой так это раньше было это
10th-10th century period Nadezhda is a Russian name
X-X век период надежда - это русское имя
in fact
по факту
then mommy Roman who was by
то мама римская кто была по
nationality by nationality
национальности по национальности
well Russian
ну русская
and how did it happen that the Pope
а как так получилось что папа римский
took mommy Roman as his wife Russian
взял себе в жёны мамы римскую русскую
well they fell in love with each other how Well
ну полюбили друг друга как
not just that so he took her as his wife
Ну не просто что так он взял её в жёну
and do you know what the daughter's name was of the Pope and
а знаешь как дочку звали папы Римского и
mommy Roman
мамы римской
and you asked the question do I know what the name of the
а вы задали вопрос знаю ли я как звали
Pope's daughter was or something like that yes yes
дочку папы Римского или что-то такое да
no I don't know Alina Alina
да нет не знаю алина алина
ha funny
ха смешно
and the Pope's name was Sergey his name was
а папы Римского звали Сергей звали
Sergey
Сергей
funny his daughter Alina Sergeevna
смешно дочка его Алина Сергеевна
and dad's last name  Roman
а фамилия у папы Римского
was and the Pope's daughter Alina
было и дочка папы Римского Алина
Sergeevna
Сергеевна
cool so what is it what do
круто
you think if
ну и что это вот как ты считаешь если бы
an angel came to you and said: "You
вот к тебе пришёл ангел и сказал: "Ты
must choose either intelligence or beauty what
должна выбрать либо ум либо красоту что
would you choose what would you choose intelligence
бы ты выбрал что бы ты выбрал ум
and why why and why is beauty needed
а почему почему а зачем красота нужна
if there is no intelligence yes intelligence yes
если нет ума да ума да
you are quite wise right why beauty
ты довольно мудра правильно зачем краста
if there is no intelligence beauty if there is no
если нет ума краста если нет
intelligence damn I adore smart girls you
ума блин вот я обожаю умных девушек
know because now there are a lot of all sorts of
знаешь потому что сейчас куча всяких
girls they are
есть девчонок такие они там
liberated here and there they can do their
раскрепощённые там и там могут сделать
own makeup on their face they can do yes
себе косметику на лицо могут сделать да
but they haven't invented makeup for the brain but you are
а косметику на мозг не придумали но ты
smart you are great you are great cool
умная ты молодец ты молодец
you like smart men smart
круто тебе нравятся умные мужчины умные
men
мужчины
I am not looking for a man for myself roughly speaking
я не ищу себе мужчины грубо говоря
relationships I am not interested in this now
отношения мне это не интересно теперь
reveal your secret where did you find out
раскройте свой секрет откуда вы узнали
my last name first name and patronymic I have a gift I have a
мою фамилию имя и отчество
gift
у меня дар у меня дар
funny good joke seriously
смешно хорошая шутка серьёзно
I am a psychic
я экстрасенс
we all understand that it is impossible to
мы все понимаем что это нереально
guess
угадать
as I am impossible to guess the century of birth and
как я нереально угадать век рождения и
death of the Pope of Rome Pope of Rome
смерти папы Римского папы Римского
well I really didn't know I just  I
ну я правда не знала я просто ноугад
said no guess I just no guess
сказала я просто ноугад я просто ноугад
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
what kind of crib is that behind you there behind
что за кроватка сзади тебя там сзади
you there what is that
тебя там
baby bed behind you
что это детская кровать сзади тебя
bed behind you yes you have a
кровать сзади тебя да у тебя есть
child you have a child
ребёнок у тебя есть ребёнок
yes how old how old am
да сколько лет сколько лет
I not yet years are you
я ещё нету лет
pregnant are you pregnant no she is only
ты беременна ты беременна нет ей только
months
месяцы
how old is the child age age I
сколько ребёнку возраст возраст
won't tell you well it's
не скажу
your child it's your child yes where is
ну это твой ребёнок это твой ребёнок да
daddy where is daddy in the army
а где папа где папа в армии
where in the army in the army I won't tell you in the SVO well
где в армии в армии не скажу на СВО
why this well I just maybe could have
ну зачем этого ну просто я может бы
said so that they wouldn't offend him there they wouldn't
сказал чтобы типа там его не обижали там
offend
его не обижали
him it's funny no one will offend him he's a contract
смешно его никто не обидит он срочный
soldier a contract soldier I won't say
контрактник контрактник не скажу
where is he now in what region in what
а где он сейчас в какой области в какой
region is
области
he in a regular one so
он в обычной
wait and where is the child sleeping now
так подожди а ребёнок сейчас где спит
where is the child sleeping now like
ребёнок сейчас где спит
this if he is a couple of months old he is You
так если ему пару месяцев он же Ты
should breastfeed you have big
грудью должна кормить у тебя большая
breasts there should be big breasts there should
грудь должна быть большая грудь должна
be
быть
m no it's not necessary to breastfeed him
м нет не обязательно его грудью кормить
and what do you feed with you feed with
а чем ты кормишь кормишь
formulas I understand listen but
на это есть смеси понял слушай а вот
look I  I heard that in Russia if a guy
смотри я слышал что в России если парень
dies in the SVO they pay 7 million is that
погибает на СВО выплачивает 7 млн это
true 7 million is that true how do I know well
правда 7 млн это правда откуда я знаю
I just heard I just don't understand do they
ну я просто слышал мне просто непонятно
pay his parents or wife or
выплачивают его родителям или жене или
children to whom to whom to wife or children to whom I don't know
детям кому жене или детям кому я не знаю
well but where would you spend 7 million
хорошо а ты вот куда бы потратила 7 млн
spent 7 million
потратила 7 млн
I
я
Well look if it turns out that way a dodo
Ну вот смотри если так получается
flies to him there a drone to him there 7
прилетает ему там дронт ему там дрон 7
million pays you you won't refuse them
млн тебе выплачивает ты же не откажешься
you won't refuse them I'll
от них ты же не откажешься от них
refuse
откажусь
for the child you won't take for the child you won't
для ребёнка не возьмёшь для ребёнка не
take no I myself will be without a husband and
возьмёшь нет я сама будешь и без мужа и
in short without 7 million and in short without 7 million well well
короче без 7 млн и короче без 7 млн
if it comes to that yes I will choose so
да ну если на то пойдёт да я выберу так
cool that is instead of
прикольно то есть вместо того чтобы
buying something for the child in short cool
ребёночку что-то купить короче прикольно
this dad for nothing at
это батя ни за что
all
вообще
kakaya very funny well really well it
кахая очень смешно ну реально ну
turns out he's just in vain
получается он просто напрасно
well let's take the fact that people are not
ну давайте возьмём тот факт что люди не
This is very And so if people are not A occupiers
Это очень А так если люди не А оккупанты
yes and occupiers yes why occupiers
да а оккупанты да почему оккупанты
occupier where is he now in what region
оккупант где он сейчас в какой области
where is he now in what region I will not say
где он сейчас в какой области я не скажу
well you see everything occupier representative of the
ну всё видишь оккупант представитель
occupation army occupation army
оккупационной армии оккупационной армии
that he is a representative of the occupation
что он представитель оккупационной
army. No army well okay the
армии.Нон армии ну хорошо
main thing is that
главное что
yours he will come
твоей он приедет
seven lemons I will not give you yes
семь лимонов я тебе не дам да
state yes state
государство да государство
let me tell you you know I just
давай я тебе скажу знаешь вот я просто
met a year ago on roulette also
встречался вот год назад вт рулетке тоже
with one girl also had a child all the
с одной девушкой тоже ребёнок был всё
guy on his own her
парень на свой её был
husband was and in short she says: "No no with him
муж и короче она говорит: "Не не с ним
everything will be fine" and I met this
будет всё нормально" а встречал вот это
2 months ago she cries tears just
2 месяца назад она ревёт слезами просто
such crocodiles and tears just flow like a
такие крокодили и слёзы прямо ну текут
river I ask what is it well I
рекой я спрашиваю что такое ну я
communicate normally yes she
нормально же общаюсь да она
says: "My Stepana
говорит: "Степана моего
in short says: "The child is small what should
короче говорит: "Ребёнок маленький что
I do now?"  I say: "Don't
теперь мне делать?" Я говорю: "Та не
cry, just pay the money." She
плачь типа ну деньги выплати" она
says: "Well, they were supposed to pay you 7 million, they
говорит: "Ну тебе должны были 7 млн
paid you three." She says: "
выплатить выплатили три" говорит: "Ты
What are you going to buy with these 3 million?"  You buy it for these
что купишь на эти 3 млн?" Купишь на эти
3 million and I say: "Well, damn, well, you can
3 млн и я говорю: "Ну блин ты ну ты им
cry to them, you wont get it back" like she
плачь ты его уже не вернёшь" типа она
says: "Damn, who needs me now
говорит: "Блин не а кому я нужна теперь
with this child?"  Like here and so uh already
с этим ребёнком?" Типа тут и так ээ уже
with this locomotive
с этим паровозом
yes I say: "Damn let me find it you seem to
да я говорю: "Блин дай найдёшь ты вроде
find it you seem" and she was about 20 years old yes she was
найдёшь ты вроде" а ей лет 20 было да
young and everything she she
она мо молоденькая была всё она она так
just changed on her face her hair turned grey
на лице просто изменилась седы волосы
and the child also something
такие стали да ребёнок тоже что-то
in short he
короче
says something happened with his digestion
говорит с пищеварением у него случилось
apparently he gets it from his mother this
видно от мамы передаётся вот это
nervousness and such well such well and she
нервничаниние и такое ну такое ну и она
too she was she thought well damn well how
тоже она была она думала ну блин ну как
she says I thought well how is this only
она говорит я думал ну как это же только
not with mine only not with mine can it be well it can't
не с моим только не с моим может быть ну
he why exactly him she
не может он не почему именно его она
says and she cries like this example she
говорит и она вот так рыдает пример
says: "Lord why exactly did they
говорит: "Господи ну почему именно его
take him?"  He says that out of 20 people in his company,
забрали?" Говорит из его роты да из 20
18 died and two remained, he
человек 18 умерло двое осталось он
says: Why couldnt he be in these
говорит: "Почему он не мог быть в этих
two?  You see, you see, and moreover,
двух?" Понимаешь понимаешь и больше того
if they are captured, it is
в плен если в плен попадают это же
thought that the occupiers can simply be there with
думает что оккупанты просто там могут
them, I dont know, so its better if, look, if
ними я не знаю поэтому лучше если смотри
anything, I can say that you are a
если что я могу сказать что вот ты
normal person, yes, we can do it for him
нормальный человек да мы можем за него
if he is captured, so that we can
если он попадёт в плен чтобы сказать
communicate with him normally, maybe
чтобы ну с ним нормально общались может
exchange him faster, because you are normal, you are
обменяли потому что ты нормальна ты же
not some woman there, eh, thats it, we will
не то что там какая-то тётка там э всё
capture you, we will capture you,
мы вас захватим мы вас захватим
I can in front of What, so that we can
я могу перед Что какой-то чтобы
discuss politics, I am a politician, yes, look, I am a
обсуждать политику я политик да смотри я
politician, I am a representative of the GUR, and we
политик я представитель ГУР а мы
communicate here in Chatuletka and find, eh, the wives of the
общаемся тут в Чатулетке и находим э жён
military, we communicate with them, yes, well, sometimes it happens, for
военных общаемся с ними да ну иногда
example, a military man wants to go over to the
бывает например военный хочет перейти на
side of Ukraine, sometimes it happens that a military man
сторону Украины иногда бывает военный
is captured, and we need to exchange our people,
попал в плен а нам нужно наших людей
yes, for these, and so we say:
обменять да на этих и вот мы говорим:
Well, we dont care who to exchange, we can
"Ну нам всё равно кого обменять мы можем
exchange, for example, if the person is
обменять например вот если человек
good, yes, then we can exchange his husband
хороший да то его мужа можем обменять
faster, give him faster, you can look, I can
быстрее дай быстрее можешь смотри я могу
write down the data just in case
записать данные на всякий случай если
he is captured, so that we can give him up
вдруг он попадёт в плен чтобы мы его
for exchange faster,
быстрее на обмен отдали быстрее
send him faster  no he will never be
намендали нет он не попадёт ни за что в
captured better watch because when he is
плен лучше смотри потому что когда уже
captured then it is already more difficult like
попадает в плен уже тогда сложнее типа
if they send him like to this
если его отправят типа в это в
concentration camp then it is bad then it is bad but
концлагерь тогда плохо тогда плохо а
if they send him like we will immediately go to the
если отправят типа мы сразу на
distribution center for exchange then he
распределитель для обмена тогда его
will be exchanged within 3 months month well
обменяют в течение 3х месяцев месяц ну
cool I know that he will not go there well
круто я-то знаю что он туда не попадёт
look in short I am not
ну смотри такое короче я ж не на это не
pressuring you for this if you want you can
давлю на тебя если хочешь можешь
leave his last name first name I will write it down for myself I will
оставить его фамилию имя я себе запишу
tell the guys that if such a thing suddenly
передам ребятам что если такой вдруг
happens suddenly yes what well it is better for him
будет вдруг да что ну его лучше потому
because he has a good girlfriend a small
что девушка у него хорошая маленький
child you understand a small child if
ребёнок понимаешь маленький ребёнок если
not there would not be a child like yes anyway but
нет не был бы ребёнок типа да всё равно
so you are a mother with a small child well a
бы а так ты мама с маленьким ребёнком ну
mother with a small child well it is
мама с маленьким ребёнком ну тебе же
better for you that your husband comes back you understand or do
лучше чтобы муж вернулся понимаешь или
you still want him 7 million yes come so that
ты так и хочешь чтобы он 7 млн да прилти
he 7 million yes turn into no he will come back anyway
чтобы он 7 млн да превратился нет он и
tell him what his name is his last name
вернётся ему вот скажи его как его зовут
and I will write it down and give it to the guys so that I will
фамилия и я запишу и дам ребятам чтобы и
give it if suddenly happens you understand this is
дам если вдруг случится понимаешь это
insurance  insurance insurance
страховка страховочка страховка
insurance no I don't need your
страховочка нет мне не нужна ваша
insurance and what's your husband's name and what's
страховка а как у тебя мужа зовут а как
your husband's name I won't tell you are you afraid
у тебя мужа зовут я не скажу боишься ну
well okay you are afraid well okay
хорошо боишься ну хорошо
you also by the way said it wrong
вы тоже кстати неправильно назвали
what what my name surname and patronymic name is
что что моё имя фамилию и отчество
possible possible
возможно возможно
oh then look
ай тогда смотри
we knew your name we have special ones
мы знал твоё имя есть специальные у
who determine it
нас которые определяют
right away saying right away but if you don't want everything right away
сразу сразу говоря а сразу не хочешь всё
we will then it will just take longer that's okay well let's
мы тогда просто дольше будет это
say they don't want to be
да ну хорошо скажем что не хотят на
exchanged if they get caught let them not go to the
обмен если попадётся пусть не идёт на
exchange to the
обмен на
exchange why do you need her why do you need her so that
обмен ну зачем она тебе ну зачем она
woman who lost her
так вот и та женщина которая потеряла
husband in the SVO she cries and sits and
мужа на СВО она плачет и сидит
says damn I thought that
говорит что блин я думала что с моим
this wouldn't happen to mine and each each one thinks
такое не случится и каждая каждая думает
that this wouldn't happen to him it won't
что с его такое не случится с его не
happen to him one starts saying: "So he's a
случится одна начинает говорить: "Так он
contract soldier alone and he's a volunteer and
контрактник один а он доброволец а он
in short damn a conscript it's not his fault
короче блин срочник он не виноват
boy" well damn there is there is there is
мальчик" ну блин есть есть есть есть
such a thing well look maximum 2 years
такое ну смотри максимум 2 года
then the child will grow up a little easier
потом ребёнок подрастёт немножко легче
then it will be easier then it will be
будет тогда будет легче тогда будет
easier
легче
because with a small child yes when the
потому что с маленьким ребёнком да когда
mother is alone and the husband, moreover, he can do more than
мама одна и муж причём он может не
just so that if there will be
просто чтобы ещё если будет безвести
missing if they don't want to
пропавший если его не будут хотят
determine it well it's impossible to determine DNA
определять ну невозможно определить ДНК
uh because of the arrival of the Heimars then there wo
ээ из-за хаймарса прилёта то тогда и
n't be any better payments without these missing
выплат не будет лучше без эти пропавшие
well and so for several years maybe you
ну и так несколько лет может быть
know years maybe you know like this and so
понимаешь лет может быть
and how would you like him to be missing for
а как бы ты хотела вот чтобы он был
2 years and then
безвести пропавший 2 года и потом
recognized or immediately recognized immediately
признали или сразу признали сразу
recognized
признали
I repeat to you again he comes
я вам ещё раз повторяю он возвращается
home after 3 months and doesn't
домой через 3 месяца и больше никуда не
go anywhere else stays with me and with my
уходит остаётся со мной и с моим
child no one comes back anywhere
ребёнком никто никуда не возвращается
show me people who returned from the SVO
покажи мне людей которые с СВО
their own returned and where did
возвращались сво возвращались а а с чего
you get the idea that he was specifically at the SVO tell me
вы взяли что он именно на СВО вот вы мне
I told you where he was what what
скажите я вам говорила где он что что
what please tell me
что что вот скажите мне пожалуйста
where you got the idea that he was at the SVO well because
откуда вы взяли что он на СВО ну потому
if he is a military man he is at the SVO because
что если он военный он на СВО потому что
if he is a military man he is at the SVO well and what does it
если он военный он на СВО ну и что
mean he is at the SVO it means he is at the SVO oh
значит он на СВО значит он на СВО ой
my god well yeah damn you know what else could be
мой ну да блин ещё знаешь что может быть
of course it could be that he could
конечно может быть что он может
come back
вернуться
for example and it would be sad because
например и это будет печально потому что
then there are no payments and you still have him  you will have to
тогда и выплат нету и тебе ещё его
support him you will also
содержать придётся тебе ещё его
have to support him oh my god why do I need
содержать придётся боже мой зачем мне
these payments you don't understand that money is so
эти выплаты вы не понимаете что деньги
yes there will be no payments and no payments so
так вот да не будет выплат и не выплат
what do you think anyway money
ну и что всё равно вы думаете деньги
decides everything in this world no no but it decides
решают всё в этом мире нет нет а решают
decides oh
решают
my god well
боже мой
let's do it this way what would you like a husband with
ну давай так что бы ты хотела мужа с
money and or a husband without money and money do
деньгами и или мужа без денег и денег
n't you think that these are too
вам не кажется что это слишком
mercenary questions I asked you to answer
меркантильные вопросы я вас просила
answer and I have every right
ответьте ответьте а я имею полное право
not to answer well then I'm not answering then yes you will take the money you will
не отвечать ну значит не отвечаю значит
take the money
да возьмёшь деньги возьмёшь деньги
priests what kind of topism do
батюшки что за топизм
you have icons at home icons at home and
а у тебя есть иконы дома иконы дома а
why do you need them well you are a believer
зачем вам это ну ты верующая
and why do you need them I would advise you to get
а зачем вам это я бы посоветовал
some kind of icon
какую-то икону
so that at least one can be
завести чтоб хотя бы одну
saved subscribe to my Telegram right
сохранить підпишись на мій Telegram прям
now os vin and
зараз ось він а
priest this is very and very important youtube
попик це дуже и дуже важливо youtube
drives us through the cards into a shadow ban and
заганяе нас через карки в тіньовий бан и
a lot of videos are not shown to people
дуже багато відео не показуется людям
sometimes are not shown  Information about the
вчасно не показуется інформація про
stream in order for us to have a short operational
стрими для того щоб ми мали оперативный
connection, subscribe directly and pop up
зв'язок підпишиться прям зараз а попик
there in the telegram okmdeo, there is also useful
там в телеграмі окмдео ще теж цікава и
information and useful information and we are in charge of a
корисна інформація и мы повин трима
permanent operational connection.
постійний оператив зв'язок
Regardless of that, Ill show you about it
Незалежно від того чи покаже вам про цей
YouTube glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube слава Україні підпишись